(Watch on KonFlix.vip)
[Episode 11]
What happened to Immortal Xin?
Her body can't retain water.
The Fish Drinking Technique
won't be effective for her for too long.
Is there any other way?
The only way
to break the Spell of Utterance
is to kill the person who cast it.
Then go kill them.
You are good at this.
She's being targeted now.
If I leave,
who will protect her?
It's not like you're the only one alive
in Chongling valley.
Miss, can you see
the golden lotus on my forehead?
I can.
What about it?
Since the day I was born,
this golden lotus
has grown with me.
I was born
on the 9th day of September.
Logically,
September is already autumn,
but the lotus
in the pond at my house
had never bloomed.
They all said it was an auspicious sign.
Sure enough.
Master!
On the day of my birth,
anomalies appeared in the sky,
and rainbow light stretched for miles.
Fun!
When I was four,
people from Tianyin Mountain came,
saying I had natural immortal perception
and a destiny with the immortals.
They wanted to take me up the mountain
to cultivate.
Young man.
I see
you have a natural immortal perception
and a great destiny with the immortals.
Would you like to
come up the mountain with me to cultivate?
[Tianyin Mountain Sect Master]
Never mind.
You have not yet
severed your ties to the mortal world.
In 20 years,
when you have severed your ties,
come to Tianyin Mountain to find me.
The golden lotus
in the pond has its own cultivation method
and now recognizes me as its master.
Though I am but a child,
I have already stepped
onto the path of cultivation.
Sure enough.
Twenty years later,
my parents passed away one after another.
I had no more attachments
in the mortal world.
-Jin Lun!
Where are you going?
Jin Lun, where are you going?
At that time,
I had already cultivated to
the Foundation Establishment Stage.
I worked hard cultivating along the way,
walking for 3 years,
and finally arrived at Tianyin Mountain.
But at the foot of the mountain,
I saw someone.
Leave quickly.
The masters of Tianyin Mountain
only come down the mountain
once every 3 to 5 years.
Begging for food here,
you will starve to death.
Your face is injured.
Bandage it with that.
I sat at the foot of the mountain
for 3 months,
but I couldn't get up
and take a single step
onto the stone stairs.
Three months later,
Master came down the mountain
and asked if I still wanted to go up.
Do you still want to go up the mountain?
Yes.
Then why don't you go?
I don't know.
Does it hurt?
Yes.
Is your mind clear now?
Do you know why now?
Since you don't know,
then go into the world and think about it.
If you figure it out after 10 years,
come back to look for me.
This year makes it the 10th year.
We meet again.
So?
I don't know.
You don't know?
I was enlightened
by my master since childhood.
My mind is calm as a millpond—
without joy or sorrow.
There is nothing in this world
that can stir my heart.
But ever since the day I met you,
my heart
has never been calm again.
I once asked others
what this feeling is.
They told me
it's called affection.
I don't understand.
To me,
I think you are more like a riddle.
But right at this moment,
with you so close to me,
I seem to
have a trace of understanding in my heart.
Making my Dao heart unsteady,
you might be my tribulation.
Perhaps if I just keep following you,
I can solve this riddle.
I don't think you have the chance
to solve it.
Power-Dissolving Powder?
It's a nice story,
but I don't like it.
I've long heard that Tianyin Mountain's
Golden Bracelet of Demon Suppression
is a top-tier magical artifact.
I didn't expect it to be with you.
Since you have heard of this treasure,
you should know
that the bracelet recognizes its master
and is long connected to my mind.
If I don't want to take it off,
no one can take it,
nor can they touch me.
Don't follow me anymore.
If there is a next time,
even Tianyin Mountain
won't be able to protect you.
Mr. Lu.
I brought you some food.
Please come in.
Is this all for me?
Yes.
But there's so much.
I can't eat it all.
I have some business recently
and need to leave the valley for a while.
I won't be able to
come take care of you often.
After I leave,
you must practice
the Fish Drinking Technique frequently.
Don't slack off.
I will.
Mr. Lu.
Is what you're going to do
dangerous?
No.
Then I hope
everything goes smoothly,
and you return safely.
Okay.
Senior Bai,
that night, I saw
Junior Jiang wound
that male cultivator with her sword.
But in the blink of an eye,
his wound healed completely.
Don't you find that a bit strange?
But Junior Jiang's Chengying Sword
is no ordinary weapon.
Even a Nascent Soul cultivator
won't be able to recover
that quickly after being injured
by it.
War Demon.
Could it be him?
Why did you come to see me?
I was worried about your illness.
Are you feeling better?
It's not completely cured yet,
but I found a way to relieve it,
so it's not terrible.
And you?
I'm much better.
Mr. Li took me to see a doctor.
How many years did Li Si serve
under your father?
Three years.
Have you seen him before?
I mean,
did you know him
before your father passed away?
So,
you didn't know him before.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm just asking.
Thank you for coming to see me.
[Pingxiang Town]
This place is neither big
nor small,
but finding someone
is not that easy.
How about asking someone?
If you put it that way,
it should be in Pingxiang Town.
I was traveling,
and then I met a
crazy man
running toward me.
Looking at his appearance,
he didn't look like someone
from the Central Plains.
He looked like he was from North Xiang.
Even people from North Xiang are coming
to beg here.
It's strange.
What do you think they're after?
That guy is a fool.
God knows what he's thinking.
Exactly.
We found him.
You're lucky.
Sirs!
Wait a minute!
What is it?
The man from North Xiang you just mentioned—
where is he?
We see him every day.
He's right in that shack ahead.
But
why are you looking for him?
That fool can't even speak.
He's starving so badly
he eats everything.
And he lies down when he's full.
Thank you.
Thank you, Sir.
You're welcome.
-We're rich!
Sirs,
is there anyone from North Xiang here?
North Xiang?
Over there.
Next door.
Thank you.
He's in a pretty bad state.
Spare me, My Lord!
Don't kill me!
Don't kill me! Don't kill me!
I won't kill you.
I just want to ask you a question.
Who asked you to pass on that message?
Your hands
don't look like they practice
with a blade.
I am good at short weapons,
and occasionally use swords.
I used to be a scout,
focusing mainly on reconnaissance.
If I ever have to fight enemies in battle,
it's probably because I'm exposed
or surrounded.
When it's really time to fight
for my life,
it doesn't matter
if I use a blade or a sword.
Rest early, Miss Xin.
Farewell.
His injuries were clearly caused by magic.
Why did he lie?
What is his purpose
in coming to Chongling Valley?
Find Li Si.
Found him.
Judging by his figure,
he seems to be the one
who fought us that night.
I have my suspicions too.
But this person carries
the Gongshan Jade Tablet.
No matter if it's him or not,
let's follow him first.
Young Sect Master,
why don't we use magic to travel?
I've scouted around the past 2 days.
There are formations everywhere
in Chongling Valley.
Let alone using magic to travel,
even if we run a bit faster,
we might trigger a formation.
What's wrong?
He is using glutinous rice flour
to test the formations.
Could he be trying to
steal the Immortality Pill?
I don't know.
Let's go.
This way.
The connection
to the paper figure is broken.
He found out.
Oh no.
What happened to him?
We don't know either.
When we were passing by,
we heard some noises,
so we came in.
Is he still alive?
Yes.
[Filled with Vitality and Grace]
Doctor,
how is Mr. Li?
He's fine.
It's just some superficial wounds.
He'll wake up soon.
Why are you all here?
What happened?
Oh no.
It's gone.
What's gone?
The Gongshan Jade Tablet.
It's gone?
I saw a dark figure earlier.
I thought it looked suspicious,
so I followed it.
I was ambushed by that person
and was knocked out.
When I woke up,
the Gongshan Jade Tablet was gone.
When you were fighting him,
did you see his face?
Was there anything notable?
It was too dark.
He was masked.
I couldn't see clearly.
I only remember...
he had a sharp gaze.
His moves
were also very vicious.
Li Si?
It really is you.
Look,
Xutuo City is right ahead.
I met him there
when I was moving
the goods.
Take a look, Sir.
Top-quality leather drums.
I saw him
right around here.
When I saw him,
he was wearing
fine silk from the Central Plains.
It looked very expensive
and finely crafted.
Are they clothes of that material?
Yes.
Don't waste your energy.
It's useless.
I didn't want to target you.
But since you found out,
I had no choice.
I have important things to do.
I can't let you ruin it.
Just bear with it here
for a couple of days.
Once I'm done,
someone will naturally come to save you.
Miss Xin.
You are a good person.
I don't want to make things difficult
for you.
But I also beg you—
don't make things difficult for me.
I remember now.
I was near here when I saw
that person then.
So he's from the Qinghong Sect.
What is the Qinghong Sect?
The Qinghong Sect in North Xiang
is known to be somewhere glorious.
It has been passed down
for a thousand years.
Legend has it that the Grandmaster
is the Phoenix God from the divine realm.
He descended to the mortal world
to help people achieve enlightenment,
relieve disasters,
and spread blessings.
How many of them are there?
They are many.
Besides the Grandmaster
and his Left and Right Guardians,
the Four Dharma Kings,
the Eight Vajras,
and the Sixteen Branch Masters...
If you add the Fire Guards,
there are at least
tens of thousands of them.
This Qinghong Sect
is the state religion.
Even our North Xiang King
is their devout follower.
How can such a small place
hold so many people?
This isn't their headquarters, is it?
Right.
This is the Qinghong Sect's
Bishui Branch.
I heard the Branch Master
is called Hewabu.
He and Dharma King Wen Yin
are cousins.
Therefore,
he holds a prominent position in the sect.
Not only has he mastered
the Indestructible Vajra Divine Physique,
but he has also learned
the magic of Divine Command.
Although the number of people
in this branch
cannot compare to the headquarters,
there are still
thousands of them.
How many doors are there?
One.
That's good.
Huh?
What are you going to do?
Don't...
Don't provoke them.
They have received
blessings from the gods.
Even 10 personal guards
under North Xiang King
can't beat one of them.
If you offend them,
you're dead.
This is none of your business anymore.
Why aren't you leaving?
If you want to get out,
you have to do something for me.
Where did you hide
your Gongshan Jade Tablet?
Give me the jade tablet,
and I'll save you immediately.
So it was you who broke into my room.
Who are you?
It doesn't matter who I am.
What matters is that
only I can save you now.
Where is the Gongshan Jade Tablet hidden?
Save me,
and I'll take you to find it.
Stop talking nonsense.
Are you going to tell me or not?
If you don't take me out,
how can I find it?
You won't tell me?
Fine.
Then I have my own ways.
The Soul Search Technique.
I didn't want
to torture you this way,
but unfortunately, you're too stubborn.
I'll just have to find it myself.
You from the Central Plains,
this is not a place you should be.
Wait for me here.
I thought so.
[Bishui Branch]
Immortal sect dog,
the fact that you made it to me alive
shows you have some skills,
and that
I raised a bunch of useless trash.
Do you know
you ruined my dinner?
What you're going to lose
isn't just your dinner,
but also your life.
Why did you kill Xin Mei?
Are you talking about that
Central Plains woman?
Is she dead?
Why did you kill her?
Why?
Because she killed Mr. Gui.
And you,
since you slaughtered so many followers
of my Phoenix God today,
go down and keep her company,
and face the Phoenix God's
punishment together.
Who...
Who are you?
One who's after your life.
I am the envoy of the Phoenix God.
My god's glory
can replace the sun and moon
and shine upon the world.
God.
Please give me the supreme power.
Through my hands,
turn this blasphemer
to ashes.
Golden Core to Nascent Soul.
Advancing right on the spot?
Master is mighty!
The Phoenix God's power is unmatched
and invincible!
Even if the Phoenix God comes,
they will have to
die with you today.
Found it.
Your jade tablet is mine now.
The Golden Body!
Ignorant mortal,
accept the wrath of the Phoenix God!
♪ I ask the Nine Heavens:
what is the purpose of this life? ♪
♪ With my spine as my monument,
I shall never kneel ♪
♪ Though this life be wretched,
I will not sink so low ♪
♪ As to become a puppet of fate ♪
♪ What is the purpose of life?
To draw my blade and slay evil ♪
♪ Even if I am turned to dust,
I will not regret ♪
♪ By my will,
I shall bring back the sun and moon ♪
♪ And restore clear radiance
to the mortal realm ♪
♪ Rather than bowing my back
to apologize to the Heavens ♪
♪ I would sooner rewrite
this fated calamity ♪
♪ I demand the story
follow my own desire ♪
♪ To serve as its final conclusion ♪
You... You will die
from a spiritual energy riot!
You...
You will bleed
from your seven orifices and die!
You will commit suicide!
You... You will die instantly!
You... drop dead!
What's going on?
Run!
It's such
a superficial Spell of Utterance—
how could you show it off,
embarrassing yourself.
I'm curious.
Spell of Utterance is a high-level spell.
Even Cave Void cultivators
find it hard to control.
You were just
a Golden Core cultivator.
How did you master it?
What did you just drink?
Why should I tell you?
The Phoenix God
will punish you.
You really are hell-bent on seeing
your own funeral, aren't you?
Would you like to see
what the real Spell of Utterance
looks like?
Your hands are covered in blood,
and you're burdened with sin.
At this moment,
you will bleed out of your seven orifices,
and your meridians will be broken off.
Calm your anger, God.
We are willing to surrender
and serve you!
Calm your anger, God.
We are willing to surrender
and serve you!
Calm your anger, God.
In this hall,
anyone who has killed
innocent people
will die by their own hands.
It's settled?
Let's go.
Have a sip.
I've recovered?
It can absorb water now?
Kill him.
Wait.
Divine Doctor Su,
please let me ask him a few questions.
When did
your plan start?
Was it after entering Chongling Valley,
when we met in the ruined temple,
or even earlier?
I don't understand what you're saying.
You broke
the mountain protection formation,
sneaked outside the Jiujue Cave,
and almost destroyed
the Dragon-Severing Stone.
I see you've put
a lot of thought
into every step you took to get here.
If you want to steal the Immortality Pill,
just say it.
Why play dumb?
What do you mean by steal?
That day at the Pill-Tasting Conference,
you
and you—
all of you
saw that I had the jade tablet.
Just because I lost my tablet,
I don't get the pill?
Miss Lyu's heart disease
can be cured
even without the Immortality Pill.
How would I know
if you're lying to me?
Full of hypocrisy.
I don't think you want
the Immortality Pill
for Miss Lyu,
but for yourself.
So...
So what if it's for myself?
Lyu Yunsu is just a mute girl.
How am I worse off than her?
I, Li Si, have outstanding talent.
I practiced sword at 7,
and reached Great Completion in swordplay
at 16.
Even when facing
Foundation Establishment Stage
cultivators,
I was not weak at all.
If you give me another hundred years,
I will be able to compete
with Golden Core cultivators.
Give me another two hundred years,
and I will be able to suppress
Soul Projection stage cultivators
with a mortal's sword,
leaving them completely defenseless.
Give me another five hundred years,
and I will enter sainthood
through the way of the sword,
becoming the first
mortal immortal in the world
to ascend with a physical body!
With my talent,
don't I deserve
an Immortality Pill?
So
your plan started from
when you met Miss Lyu.
You are not
General Lyu's subordinate at all.
Escorting General Lyu's orphan
into the valley
was just an excuse for you.
It was all for the Immortality Pill.
Along the way,
how many people
have you tricked into risking their lives?
Even if I did use Lyu Yunsu,
if it weren't for me,
she would have died
among the refugees long ago.
Would she still be alive now?
I just didn't expect
that your Chongling Valley
would collude with those immortal sects,
allowing them in the valley
to steal and rob,
and steal my Gongshan Jade Tablet.
You...
Don't make false accusations!
Whatever.
Now that I've been caught by you,
it is my fate.
I have nothing to say.
Su Taiyi!
You shameless old thief!
You will die a horrible death!
I'll kill you!
The alchemy furnace is not yet ready.
He who hurts the divine doctor
must not be spared.
Miss Lyu.
Miss Lyu!
[Chongling Valley]
Who's there?